THIS FILM IS A WORK OF FICTION
CREATED FOR ENTERTAINMENT PURPOSES ONLY
DUBAI
Get the gauze and notify the doctor.
He needs the blood now.
OUT OF 8 BILLION PEOPLE ON EARTH
ONLY 0.00000625%
HAVE THE RAREST BLOOD TYPE
FOR THOSE WHO NEED IT,
THIS BLOOD TYPE CAN MEAN LIFE OR DEATH
THEY CALL THEMSELVES AURUM BLOOD
You know,
if we take any more blood from him,
he'll die.
So be it. My boss must live.
But you have to think of what--
I'll find another.
Aurum blood isn't something
you can just find.
Do as I say.
And keep all his organs.
We may need them later.
Get me the new source. Forget the cost.
Okay, I'm on it.
VIETNAM
Whoa.
The choice is yours to make.
Whatever way
you want them to die can be done.
A car accident, poisoning.
We'll make it look like a suicide.
If the target has protection,
we can take them out as well.
I'll send you our package
and price list, okay?
We can talk when I'm back in the office.
I'm busy right now.
All right.
So this kid,
you really think she's gonna be the one?
We're both gonna find out together.
Hey.
You've cleared everything
with the parents, right?
No problems.
They'll allow her to come with us.
The payment's been made.
Up. Get up.
Who the hell are you?
Hey, the girl's in a bad way.
MY DEAREST ASSASSIN
Hm.
I can't think of any assassin houses
using a gun like this.
Who do you think that guy is?
He's got to be a Hunter.
Freelance assassin hire.
Paid to find anything for anyone.
People, animals, objects.
As long as the price is right,
they'll get it.
Do you know who took the girl?
Since you already took
part of the payment,
that will put you in debt with us.
If you can find an Aurum blood,
whether it be a new one or an old one…
I don't care.
You must find one.
What do you think? He working contract?
Or maybe hunting on the open market.
There's a market out there,
whether it's organs or blood.
This is not going to be easy for us.
We're gonna need to keep
a close eye on her.
I get the feeling
everyone's gonna be after this girl.
BANGKOK
Hey, wait.
Hey.
No one's gonna hurt you, okay?
Come on, hurry!
Hello. Here you are welcome.
Everyone here is friendly.
We will care for you
just like family, okay?
Hey!
Hey.
Wait up.
Look.
Hey, nice one.
-Hey!
-Follow her.
Hey.
-Easy, easy, easy.
-Back up.
-Wait, wait, wait. Hey.
-Calm down, please.
-Hey.
-It's okay.
Be calm.
You're bleeding. You're bleeding.
Bleeding.
Oh my.
Okay. This will just sting a little bit,
but that's definitely
gonna leave a scar, dear.
It's nasty.
I need to take a little blood.
Is that okay?
Little sting.
She has no one left
who can look after her.
Could you be there for her?
It's why I brought her here,
to our family.
Just like M?
Back then,
when I first arrived here,
I had no idea
why these people had saved me.
Or why I had to stay.
But as soon as I looked into his eyes,
he made me feel calm.
And I knew
that he was someone I could trust.
This young girl's blood is compatible
with any RH null blood type.
You're a very lucky man.
Cases like this are unbelievably rare.
Could her parents have had the same blood?
It may be recessive genes coming together.
-So when can we start collecting?
-Patience.
She's still far too young.
Once the blood is drawn,
it will only last 40 days.
Remember, with blood,
it's best to keep it warm in the host.
I became a member of House 89
through no choice of my own.
A place that looks like
a typical antique shop,
except it's not.
The only thing
that I am free to do in this house
is remember the one person
who took everything from me.
Hm.
Keep a close watch on her.
Under no circumstances
does she leave the house.
Rain.
Rain. Rain.
Pran.
Lhan.
Hey, what's going on?
Come in. You're gonna catch a cold.
No, you come here.
-Huh?
-M, come on.
-Don't be scared.
-What do you mean? No way.
-Come on, M, let's go!
-What are you doing?
Scared of rain?
Hm.
Your turn.
INDIA
-How long will it take?
-A couple of minutes. We'll see results.
-Has the report been confirmed?
-Get out of here.
-Where do these people come from?
-Come over here. Check this.
It's fine, brother. It's negative.
All confirmed Rh type,
but not the blood we want.
Keep it cool.
I know you're not, but listen to me.
There's a lot of people in this country.
Some may have fallen off the grid.
Shit.
Ugh, ah.
There's none here.
It's been a long time since we last found
anyone with Aurum blood.
You have to go back to Vietnam
and find the one who knows
where they took her.
Vietnam?
I don't think
the ones who took her are Hunters, okay?
I don't even know who they are.
I'm afraid that--
You've already gotten 20 million.
Even if they are God,
you bring her back.
Why does M have to practice so much?
So full on.
It's a duty.
Everyone in the house has a role.
What's mine? What's my role?
Nothing.
I guess.
Why not?
Then what about you?
I don't have one either.
Caring for you.
Your job is to keep me at home.
You're safe more than anywhere.
I'm safe locked inside.
That's called fear.
Not strong enough.
Haven't trained enough. Not fast enough.
Come on, kiddo.
Do your job.
-Hm.
-Hm, hm, hm.
Mm.
You're too predictable for him.
He knows
when you're gonna move left or right.
Come on.
Try it with me.
Uh-huh.
Okay.
You ready?
Yeah. Okay.
Hey!
When did you learn?
Uh…
This guy, he's been making me
teach him for years.
He never lets me sleep.
Hey.
It's our secret.
Go again.
Yeah, okay.
Come on.
Yeah.
-Ah!
-You see?
You need to flip your moves.
Switch it front to back.
Go right, not left.
Shit. You're right, man.
You'll catch him off guard,
and then you can get in close.
Once you're in control of the distance,
then you can choose your attack.
And it's about finding
and exploiting his weaknesses.
What if we don't know who we're fighting?
How do you know their weakness?
Then you have to take a hit first
to find out.
Too much to drink,
and the birthday boy's out cold.
Why don't you tell your dad?
You can fight.
And you're good at it.
I'm sure he doesn't want me
doing the work he does.
And having to go outside.
Do you really just wanna sell antiques?
Honestly. Or do you want to go outside?
I guess it's just
how I was raised.
I don't really know
what I actually want.
I like taking care of you.
That's something…
good.
Now,
is there anything you really want to do?
Hm?
Mm…
There is,
but I wouldn't know where I'd even begin.
We're done.
Here.
Hm? Mm.
In here.
-Hey. No.
-Ah.
-Come on, leave me alone.
-Stay.
This next job, the target always has
four guards with him.
Entry and exit points
are listed on the map that I gave you.
I also have word that other houses
might also make a move on our job.
Damn, not sounding easy.
Should M be involved?
What's the thinking?
Yeah. Why not.
I think he's ready.
Then finish eating.
-We'll continue this in the office.
-Mhm.
Go.
Hm.
Hey.
Want to go out and have fun?
Look okay?
What about the hair?
Up.
Down.
Uh…
Very pretty.
What's the occasion?
I'm going out.
Pran's taking me out.
Don't tell him this is what I'm wearing.
What did the uncles say?
We're just gonna sneak out.
No one'll be home to know.
Not a word, okay?
You think he'll like it?
He will.
He'd be crazy not to.
When do I get my turn, Dad?
Go. Everyone get ready.
Ma'am, this way.
What is this?
And it's worth what?
Crap, so crap, it's bad.
I look better. Huh.
House 89.
Then hurry up.
Mala.
Shit.
What now?
The target is in Zone One.
Four bodyguards with him.
Take out the Mala gang first,
then take out the target.
Did you wear your non-slip shoes, darling?
You don't want to slip
in filthy blood, hm?
They'll be okay.
Dealing with how you describe your blood.
Plan B.
M's the only one they won't recognize.
Time to show them what you've got, kid.
-This way, sir.
-This way.
Hey, get down, sir, get down.
We move, come on.
-Out of the way now. Don't stop.
-Hey!
The target has entered the kill zone.
Come on!
Take him out.
Come on. Move!
-Move.
-You against the wall.
Come on. Move, sir, come on.
Move, move, move. Come on. Move!
Hey, hey. Hey, boss, boss.
Hey, sir, sir. Boss, boss!
Boss!
Kill confirmed.
The target's been eliminated.
Not bad for your first job, kid.
House 89, mission accomplished.
Here's Amber Hymns by Enoch Rayburne.
The rare hand-pressed final edition.
You are one of 14 people
in the world with a copy.
I like how it sounds. One of 14.
I do as well.
Owning something
with such limited quantity,
it makes you feel…
magnifique.
Yeah.
I hear that you're back
in Thailand for a while.
Are you here to relax,
or you're hunting something for a client?
Hm. Honestly,
I'm looking for something very important
and feel like I'm close to finding it.
How can you be so sure?
'Cause I'm a Hunter.
And I can almost smell it.
Where did you get that?
Do you like it?
Very much.
Hair up or down?
Can I get three of these
and three sausage ones?
Hm?
Here you go.
-How much?
-Sixty baht.
You like?
Mm.
Wo, wo, wo, wow!
Hello, handsome.
Good evening, Miss Chaba,
and to you, Blue.
Wow.
If you're ready to accept the job,
I have the first payment.
If you accept.
Fucking hell!
What problem do you have with this house?
They took something of mine
and wasted my time tracking it down.
Everyone in this house is a killer.
Mm.
That's exactly why I'm here.
Hit men to kill other hit men.
It's maintaining a balance.
I heard a few days ago
House 89 lost you a lot of money.
Now here's something
for you to think about.
If House 89 was out of the picture,
imagine how much money you could make.
I hear you went out
of the house last night.
We're out there working our asses off.
Somehow, you think rules don't apply.
Let me go out with you sometime.
I need something to do.
What you've been asked to do
is care for Lhan.
And I'm doing that.
Isn't taking her out looking after her?
Her whole time she doesn't go outside.
What sort of life's that?
Everyone here has their own life,
you realize?
But you're not thinking
of anyone else's life,
only your own selfish wants and needs.
Selfish how?
What do I want that's so different?
Wanting Lhan to see life
outside the house.
What's so wrong about that?
You told me to look after her.
I'm doing it.
Why won't you let me do it my own way?
If something does actually go down,
all of that practice
you think you're doing in secret
won't be enough to protect you.
My turn now.
The reason M can beat everyone,
including yourself,
is because of me.
I taught him what to do.
You didn't know.
Never trained your son.
There are people hunting her
outside of this house.
There's a price on her head.
Do you not get that?
What do you mean a price on her head?
How come they want her, Dad?
Why would there be a price?
Why?
-Why won't you tell me?
-People are willing to pay for her blood!
Dad.
You don't understand what it means.
Why she's here,
and why I worked so hard to find her.
There's a bigger picture
that you just don't get,
and yet you run around
doing your own thing.
You know,
maybe I need to separate both of you.
Stop!
I know that you love her.
I can see it.
If Lhan stays here in the house,
she will be safe.
But she doesn't go outside.
Not everyone
gets to live the life they want.
They live the life they have to.
Accept this!
It will get easier.
Go home?
Mm-hmm.
Or pick somewhere.
As long as you and I are together.
I will take care of you.
What about the others? And M?
He can't know yet.
We'll figure it out
once we get out of here.
Hurry up and pack. We'll leave tonight.
PRAN
JUST LEFT MY ROOM
Wait.
Leave the woman.
Let's go. Stay close.
Hey, get down.
You guys okay?
Go!
Lhan. Lhan!
Stop.
Pran!
Hey!
Clear!
Sit him down here.
-Come here, Lhan.
-Take her!
Come on.
Down, down.
-Uncle! What are you doing?
-Come down, Lhan. Back off. Go!
-Hold her down.
-Uncle! Uncle!
Hurry up, Doc!
Hold him still.
Just a second.
Stay still.
Calm down.
-Are you okay?
-Hurry up. Get on with it!
Lhek, set up the other bed.
M, come here. Hurry.
-Okay.
-Come on.
Pran, Pran, I'm here.
Hey, the bleeding won't stop.
Keep pressure on it, nice and firm.
Keep pressing.
-Stay still.
-Shit.
Let's go!
Come on!
Pran, Pran.
Pran.
It's coming.
Doc!
Don't.
Dad.
Please don't.
-Understand.
-Dad.
-Let go of me.
-Come here.
Leave me alone.
-On the table.
-Lay down. Lay down.
-Pran…
Stay down. Just hold still, okay?
And up. Hold his legs down, quick, hurry.
Fuck you.
-It's okay.
-I don't want it.
Hold him down.
-Let me go.
-Hold him!
-I don't fucking want this.
-Stay still.
Stay.
Just keep holding him down.
Stay still.
-The needle.
-Come on.
Let her go.
M.
Get her out of here. M.
It's okay.
Pran needs Aurum blood.
He's also a hemophiliac.
It was then that I realized
that I was brought to the house
to be his blood bank.
Deaw!
Hey! Open the door!
Are you gonna open or not?
Open the door!
Or your friends are dead.
I'm beginning the count.
One…
Two…
-You're crazy.
-Oh, yeah.
They're not gonna open it.
Will he make it out of here?
He needs to have
more clotting factor to help.
You've already given him one.
You said we have to fight our way out.
Then he needs another shot.
He needs it now.
You okay?
Yep.
Ready to fight with your dad?
All right.
Hey, hey.
-Hey, shit.
-Go! Go! Get out of here. Quick!
Dad.
Shit. Hey, hey.
Shit.
The system's been hacked.
We're locked in.
Get everyone out! I'll handle this.
-Hey, Doc. Quick!
-Uncle!
-Dad. Dad!
-Pran!
No.
-Dad.
-No!
Dad!
-Don't.
-Dad.
-We gotta go.
-Dad!
Let's go. Hurry!
Okay.
Bomb!
Dad!
Pran.
We have to go now.
-Let's go. Let's go.
-Get off me, Uncle.
We gotta go. We gotta go now.
Pran, hurry, son. We gotta go.
-Uncle.
-You have to leave.
You have to leave him.
Calm down.
Enough, kid. Pull yourself together.
Pull yourself together!
Go.
They all died, so that we can live.
Do you understand? Let's go. Hurry.
Uncle.
Let's go.
Dad. Dad!
PRIVATE PROPERTY
NO TRESPASSING
Lhan.
Where are you going, Lhan?
Away from here.
Wait. This is the safest place right now.
No one is safe. Not if I'm here.
We're all in this together, Lhan.
Seriously? How can you say that?
My father and mother are dead.
We're all gonna be wiped out.
Because of me.
You can't blame yourself.
Listen to me.
Lhan, everyone in this house loves you.
Love?
Is it me they love? Or my blood they want?
I'd give anything,
anything to the people I love.
But not like this.
You have all been lying to me.
-Even you've never said anything.
-I had no idea!
I didn't know, okay? Pran didn't either.
How could we know about your blood type?
The uncles brought you to the house.
Said you had no family left.
Why should we think anything's different?
I don't have anyone else either.
I know you think they have failed you.
They failed me too.
Pran will be hurting the most.
But believe me,
this is the best place, right here.
And the two of you
are so lucky to have found each other.
Let's go home, Lhan.
Pran, hold up.
Wait. Come on.
Take it easy. Take it easy now, okay?
You're recovering
faster than I thought, kid.
At this rate, a couple of months,
and you'll be back to normal.
Doc…
I know Dad put aside some money for Lhan.
He told me.
Can you and M find Lhan a place to stay?
Take her somewhere safe, please.
Make sure she's safe and doing okay.
-Then we can go our separate ways.
-Separate ways?
Go where?
I just want her safe.
I want everyone to be safe.
We can't lose anyone else.
But there's not a safe place
that we can go.
Lhan will be hunted.
We will be killed.
The Mala gang has to wipe us out.
Otherwise, they die.
It's the way our world is.
It's kill or be killed.
No one is going to be safe
until everyone's dead.
The day I asked you to run away…
that was the day I found out
you had golden blood.
I never knew
why Dad had brought you to the house.
I assumed to protect you,
just like with M.
I'm so sorry.
On behalf of my dad and everyone,
I'm sorry.
Can you forgive me?
I apologize.
Lhan.
-You--
-I always feel the pain right here.
It's always there
when I think about my parents.
I have to swallow it down every time.
And it's never easy.
I've had two homes in my life.
And because of me,
people are dying in here now.
Just like it was in my first.
If there is nowhere in this world
safe for me to be,
then I have to be able to protect myself.
Am I right?
Pran.
Teach me how to kill.
I don't want to be in the back seat.
A fragile little girl
who needs everyone to protect me.
I wanna watch them die with my own eyes.
I just want to be an assassin.
Just because you've decided you want to,
it doesn't mean you can be one.
Hm? People can spend
their whole lives training to be one.
We'll go as far as we can.
If she at least knows
how to protect herself,
it's better for everyone.
And if she can protect herself,
then she chooses whether she goes or not.
It's her choice.
You're so casual about it all.
You're putting her in danger.
We're up against assassins.
Not a grandma.
Let's do what Pran was saying.
It is what it is.
Maybe the grandmother
is worse than a killer.
-You ready?
-What?
Come on. Come on.
-Uh…
-Bring it.
Uh…
Shit.
-Come on.
-Huh?
Get in.
Your thinking and reactions are good.
Leg power, punches are your weak points.
Speed, flexibility,
and accuracy need work.
Impulsive.
Hey, you're just charging in.
Know your limits.
Fight like that,
you're dying before grandma.
If you're serious, let's begin.
Tactics, combat, weapons, strength.
There's a lot to learn quickly.
If you want to be a killer,
you start by being unkillable.
Begin.
Hm.
Very good.
Keep pulling. Needle tip up, okay.
Again.
Get up.
Up. Go again.
Tense up.
And breathe. Let's go.
Again.
Wow. Hey.
Nice work.
If I don't make it…
can you look after her?
Pran,
what are you saying?
You can't think like that.
Just saying, if I do, you look after her.
I don't want her left alone.
Have you even realized
that I care for her too?
Sure.
I can see it for miles.
When
do you think they'll find us?
Hello, sir.
Are you after anything in particular?
USED CAR DEALERSHIP
This van, has it been here long?
A little while, but not that long.
NO DOWN PAYMENT
Move.
Here you are.
Okay.
Hmm.
Okay,
it says two months.
Can you tell me where they went?
You need a lot of force
to hit a critical organ or artery.
And luck.
The skill of a surgeon.
Vital points are hard to reach.
The body is built to protect itself.
Look at it like armor,
with the rib cage here.
It's protecting the critical arteries
tucked in behind it.
I'm sorry.
Let me explain better.
Here.
These two points are crucial.
Hard to hit from distance.
But in close, it's lethal
with a quick stab or a cut.
Okay?
Remember it, Lhan.
-Wouldn't the stomach be easier?
-Uh…
Not really.
In fact, the main artery,
the aorta,
starts at the left of the heart.
But then curves around to the back.
Down the spine.
Through the diaphragm.
Into the abdomen.
Protected in deep.
Covered by fat and skin,
muscle as well.
For a fatal blow,
you must be close enough,
and fully commit yourself.
It's the only way.
-I'll go again.
-Lhan.
Once you know
how to take care of yourself…
will you please stay?
Edge of the ocean
I fall in slow motion
What if
You just stay?
Here in the blue fade
Here
Under the cold wave
I can't leave you
Telling yourself
That you can't no more
Tell me right now
What you loved me for
If you don't know, then I don't know
If you don't know
Then I don't know you
Oh
I don't wanna say
I don't wanna say it
Who's hungry?
-Oh.
-Oh, wow.
Thank you.
This looks just like Ja would make.
Did she teach you?
I watch. I learn.
Mm.
Delicious.
If Deaw was here,
he would have eaten five serves by now.
If we want to live our own way…
how do we get there together?
If we run…
we always run.
If we hide,
we keep doing as we're doing.
If we fight,
the end will come.
We just don't know how.
If I ask you to fight
without knowing how it ends…
who joins me?
We do.
Hey, wait, wait, wait, wait.
How many are we?
How do we win?
A plan, huh? Huh?
We turn the tables.
Be the hunters, not the hunted.
We stop hiding and take the fight to them.
Don't forget.
No harm is to come
to the man and the woman.
The rest of them do what you want.
Why so special?
Do they give good karma?
Is that what you need?
I control my own fate.
I have my own men here too,
but don't worry about the bounty.
It's all yours.
I want you to give me a call
if anyone comes by asking about my car.
Hello.
Someone came to the shop.
They were asking about your car.
Go.
Shit. Shit.
Hey!
Come on.
Doc!
Mm.
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Pran.
Where's everyone? Where are they?
Okay, let's go.
Lhan.
Shit!
-What do we do?
-Just drive quick!
Lhan. Lhan.
M, take us to a hospital.
Where is it? Where's the hospital? Where?
Lhan.
You'll be okay.
The bullet went through. You'll be okay.
M, she's going into shock.
-She needs blood.
-You can't, Pran.
Just stop, okay?
Stop the car.
-How are you gonna do this?
-Doc was always prepared.
Damn it!
M, I need your help.
Okay.
Lifting.
Pran.
But you're going to die.
After I do this,
just get me to a hospital.
Let's go.
Shit.
-M.
-Shit.
-M?
-I'm fine.
Stay. Wait here.
M.
-You have to stay here.
-M.
M? M!
Lhan.
You piece of shit.
Get off me.
Yeah, I know she likes you.
She really does.
She likes being with you.
-That's why you gotta survive.
-Yeah, and you as well.
We're all in this together.
We look out for her. We always have.
Hm.
Hm. Hm.
Time to live your life
the way you always wanted.
I'll always be with you.
Pran.
Hey, Pran.
Time to live your life
the way you always wanted.
I'll always be with you.
VIETNAM
This child has
the rarest blood type in the world.
He must learn to take care of himself.
He deserves the freedom to live his life
without being afraid of anything.
A freedom that so many people
gave to me.
And for the rest of the life
that I have left,
I won't let a single drop of blood
leave my body again.
Because it's not just my blood anymore,
it's the blood of the one I love
flowing together with mine.
I'm sorry to have kept you waiting.
Very hard to find.